<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<resultslist>

<results>
<label>0001</label>
<query>"magento"</query>
<totalresults>4520000</totalresults>
<startindex>1</startindex>
<starttime>1443900215854</starttime>
<endtime>1443900220640</endtime>
<elapsedtime>4786</elapsedtime>
<fatalerror>0</fatalerror>
<result>
<url>http://magento.com/</url>
<title>Magento: eCommerce Software &amp; eCommerce Platform Solutions</title>
<snippet>Magento is the eCommerce software and platform trusted by the world's leading brands. Grow your online business with Magento.</snippet>
</result>
<result>
<url>https://www.magentocommerce.com/download</url>
<title>Open Source Ecommerce Software &amp; Solutions | Magento</title>
<snippet>Magento Community Edition is open source eCommerce software used to power hundreds of thousands of online stores. It can be downloaded for free and is ...</snippet>
</result>
<result>
<url>http://magento.com/products/overview</url>
<title>Community &amp; Enterprise eCommerce Solutions | Magento</title>
<snippet>Magento Enterprise Edition is the high performance, scalable eCommerce solution for fast-growing and large businesses. It has the enterprise-class features ...</snippet>
</result>
<result>
<url>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Magento</url>
<title>Magento - Wikipedia, the free encyclopedia</title>
<snippet>Magento is an open-source content management system for e-commerce web sites. The software was originally developed by Varien Inc., a US private company ...</snippet>
</result>
<result>
<url>https://magento.com/blog</url>
<title>Magento eCommerce Blog | Magento</title>
<snippet>Grow your online business with the help of Magento's eCommerce Blog. Find many articles and resources to enhance your online business!</snippet>
</result>
<result>
<url>https://twitter.com/magento</url>
<title>Magento (@magento) | Twitter</title>
<snippet>The latest Tweets from Magento (@magento). Flexible eCommerce solutions, a vibrant extensions marketplace and an open global ecosystem. Los Angeles ...</snippet>
</result>
<result>
<url>http://www.magentocommerce.com/magento-connect/</url>
<title>Magento Connect - The Magento Extension Marketplace</title>
<snippet>Merchants with Magento as their eCommerce platform use extensions to make their online stores to do even more. Magento Connect is the largest eCommerce  ...</snippet>
</result>
<result>
<url>https://community.magento.com/</url>
<title>Magento Forums: Home</title>
<snippet>Use this forum to post any design and/or layout questions for Magento 1.x. ... All Magento 1.x technical issues that are unrelated to the installation process ...</snippet>
</result>
<result>
<url>http://smallbusiness.magento.com/</url>
<title>Magento: Small Business eCommerce Solutions</title>
<snippet>Powerful eCommerce software for small businesses designed by Magento partners.</snippet>
</result>
<result>
<url>https://github.com/magento/magento2</url>
<title>magento/magento2 · GitHub</title>
<snippet>All Submissions you make to Magento, an eBay Inc. company (“Magento”) through GitHub are subject to the following terms and conditions: (1) You grant ...</snippet>
</result>
<result>
<url>http://themeforest.net/category/ecommerce/magento</url>
<title>600+ Magento Themes &amp; Templates | ThemeForest</title>
<snippet>Create an online store with Magento themes and Magento templates. ThemeForest is the #1 marketplace for premium website themes.</snippet>
</result>
<result>
<url>http://imagine.magento.com/</url>
<title>Magento Imagine</title>
<snippet>Pay it Forward. Hurry and Submit! Inspire the ecosystem to run farther, faster. Coach best practices that work. Position companies and professionals for success ...</snippet>
</result>
<result>
<url>http://merch.docs.magento.com/ce/user_guide/Magento_Community_Edition_User_Guide.html</url>
<title>Magento Community Edition User Guide - Getting Started</title>
<snippet>Sep 24, 2015
Welcome to the online version of the Magento Community Edition User Guide! This is where you'll find the most up-to-date documentation for ...</snippet>
</result>
<result>
<url>https://enterprise.magento.com/fashion/overview</url>
<title>Magento for Fashion</title>
<snippet>Most eCommerce solutions are one-size-fits-all, but your business is unique. That's why Magento Enterprise Edition was built to be tailored to your needs. xpress.</snippet>
</result>
<result>
<url>http://magento.stackexchange.com/</url>
<title>Magento Stack Exchange</title>
<snippet>Magento Stack Exchange is a question and answer site for users of the Magento ... Magento admin panel give Fatal error: Class “Helper_Data” not Found.</snippet>
</result>
<result>
<url>http://devdocs.magento.com/</url>
<title>Magento 2 Developer Documentation</title>
<snippet>Magento 2 Developer's Guide. ... What is Magento? How the Magento platform is organized, overview of modules, file system, and database.</snippet>
</result>
<result>
<url>https://www.facebook.com/magento</url>
<title>Magento</title>
<snippet>Magento, Culver City, California. 16995 likes · 173 talking about this. Magento offers flexible, scalable eCommerce solutions designed to help...</snippet>
</result>
<result>
<url>https://www.nexcess.net/magento/hosting</url>
<title>Magento eCommerce hosting – Nexcess</title>
<snippet>Our Magento SIP Plans provide the most stable, secure, and scalable built-in Magento hosting solutions. Each Secure Isolated Platform (SIP) is an entirely ...</snippet>
</result>
<result>
<url>http://www.templatemonster.com/magento-themes.php</url>
<title>Magento Themes | Magento Templates | Template Monster</title>
<snippet>760+ premium Magento themes by Template Monster – that's responsive design, rich functionality, outstanding selection of topics. Awesome 24/7 support ...</snippet>
</result>
<result>
<url>https://partners.magento.com/english/</url>
<title>Become a Magento Partner | Magento</title>
<snippet>Magento partners establish a strategic relationship that helps them grow and succeed. See what it means to be a Solution, Technology, and Hosting Partner.</snippet>
</result>
</results>

</resultslist>

